crushpath.com 2016-03-10

# Privacy Policy | Crushpath

### Privacy Policy

Last Revised: June 12, 2012 

Crushpath LLC ("Company") is committed to protecting your privacy.We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of our website, located at www.crushpath.com ("Site") and Services (as defined in the Terms of Service). Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given in our Terms of Service located at http://www.crushpath.com/terms/index.html.

**1.) User Consent.** By submitting Personal Data through our Site or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**2.) A Note to Users Outside of the United States.Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.**

**3.) Types of Data We Collect.** "Personal Data" means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data."Anonymous Data" means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons.We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below.

**a.) Information You Provide to Us.**

We may collect Personal Data from you, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, phone number, company name, password, role, title, types of sales/industry, and sales methodology when you create an account to log in to our network ("Account"). 

You may also voluntarily provide us additional profile information at your discretion, such as your Twitter ID and personal image. 

When you order Services on our Site, our third party service provider Recurly will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, and billing information. 

If you link a Third Party Account (as defined in the Terms of Service, e.g., LinkedIn) to your Crushpath Account, we will collect your Third Party Account login credentials and collect/access Third Party Account Content to provide you the Service.You may also voluntarily provide us additional information in connection with your Third Party Account Content (e.g., filing in information not available on LinkedIn). 

We retain information on your behalf, such as files and messages that you store using your Account. 

If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply. 

When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information. 

When you post messages on the message boards of our Site, the information contained in your posting will be stored on our servers and other users will be able to see it. 

We may also collect Personal Data, such as at other points in our Site that state that Personal Data is being collected. 

**b.) Information Collected via Technology.**

To make our Site and Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. 

We also use cookies and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed."Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site.We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site.Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

**c.) Information Collected from You About Others.**

If you decide to invite a third party to create an Account, we will collect your and the third party’s names and e-mail addresses in order to send an e-mail and follow up with the third party.You or the third party may contact us at support@crushpath.com to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**4.) Use of Your Personal Data**

**a.) General Use.** In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better.We use your Personal Data in the following ways: 

facilitate the creation of and secure your Account on our network; 

identify you as a user in our system; 

provide improved administration of our Site and Services; 

provide the Services you request; 

process your order; 

improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Site and Services; 

send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your Account was created; 

send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; 

respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests; 

make telephone calls to you, from time to time, as a part of secondary fraud protection or to solicit your feedback; and 

send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to our Services and for other marketing purposes of Company. 

**b.) Creation of Anonymous Data.** We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you.We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve Site navigation.Company reserves the right to use Anonymous Data for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties in its sole discretion. 

**5.) Disclosure of Your Personal Data.** We disclose your Personal Data as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. 

**a.) Authorized Users.** The following profile information will be shared with your Authorized Users: full name, display name, title, mobile number and Twitter ID. To facilitate Authorized Users from the same Company with connecting with each other, we may provide Authorized Users with a list of, or otherwise notify Authorized Users of, other Authorized Users from their Company. 

**b.) Third Party Service Providers.** We may share your Personal Data with third party service providers to:provide you with the Services that we offer you through our Site; to conduct quality assurance testing; to facilitate creation of accounts; to provide technical support; and/or to provide other services to the Company.These third party service providers are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by Company. 

**c.) Affiliates and Acquisitions.** We may share some or all of your Personal Data with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control ("Affiliates"), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**d.) Other Disclosures.** Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), Company may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) in connection with any legal investigation; (b) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Company; © to protect or defend the rights or property of Company or users of the Services; and/or (d) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or Terms of Service. 

**6.) Third Party Data Collection.**

**a.) Third Party Accounts.** If you associate your Crushpath Account with your Third Party Account (e.g., LinkedIn), we may receive Personal and/or Anonymous Data about you from such Third Party Account, in accordance with elections.If you elect to share your information with a Third Party Account, we will share information with them in accordance with your elections.The Third Party Account’s terms and conditions (e.g., terms of use and privacy policy) will apply to the information we disclose to them. 

**b.) Third Party Websites.** When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you.We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content.Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites. 

**7.) Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Data**

**a.) Marketing Provided by Crushpath.** We will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our Site or Services.When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly at support@crushpath.com.Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communication, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy. 

**b.) Changes to Personal Data.** You may change any of your Personal Data in your Account by editing your profile within your Account or by sending an e-mail to us at the e-mail address set forth below. You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us, but please note that we may be required to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements).When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.We may retain your information for fraud or similar purposes. 

**8.) Security of Your Personal Data.** Company is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data.We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.We also require you to enter a password to access your Account information. Please do not disclose your Account password to unauthorized people.No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while Company uses reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, Company cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**9.) Contact Information.** Company welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy.Please e-mail us at privacy@crushpath.com or contact us at the following address or phone number: 

Crushpath LLC  
Attention: Admin  
2012 16th St.  
San Francisco, CA 94110  

**9.) Changes to This Privacy Policy.** This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Site.Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Site.These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Service.Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail address.In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes.If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your Account with us.Continued use of our Site or Service, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
